[
  {
    "id": "T5B01",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "How many milliamperes is 1.5 amperes?",
    "answers": [
      "15 milliamperes",
      "150 milliamperes",
      "1500 milliamperes",
      "15,000 milliamperes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5B02",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Which is equal to 1,500,000 hertz?",
    "answers": [
      "1500 kHz",
      "1500 MHz",
      "15 GHz",
      "150 kHz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5B03",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which is equal to one kilovolt?",
    "answers": [
      "One one-thousandth of a volt",
      "One hundred volts",
      "One thousand volts",
      "One million volts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5B04",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Which is equal to one microvolt?",
    "answers": [
      "One one-millionth of a volt",
      "One million volts",
      "One thousand kilovolts",
      "One one-thousandth of a volt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5B05",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which is equal to 500 milliwatts?",
    "answers": [
      "0.02 watts",
      "0.5 watts",
      "5 watts",
      "50 watts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5B06",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "Which is equal to 3000 milliamperes?",
    "answers": [
      "0.003 amperes",
      "0.3 amperes",
      "3,000,000 amperes",
      "3 amperes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5B07",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which is equal to 3.525 MHz?",
    "answers": [
      "0.003525 kHz",
      "35.25 kHz",
      "3525 kHz",
      "3,525,000 kHz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5B08",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which is equal to 1,000,000 picofarads?",
    "answers": [
      "0.001 microfarads",
      "1 microfarad",
      "1000 microfarads",
      "1,000,000,000 microfarads"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5B09",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which decibel value most closely represents a power increase from 5 watts to 10 watts?",
    "answers": [
      "2 dB",
      "3 dB",
      "5 dB",
      "10 dB"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5B10",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which decibel value most closely represents a power decrease from 12 watts to 3 watts?",
    "answers": [
      "-1 dB",
      "-3 dB",
      "-6 dB",
      "-9 dB"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5B11",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Which decibel value represents a power increase from 20 watts to 200 watts?",
    "answers": [
      "10 dB",
      "12 dB",
      "18 dB",
      "28 dB"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5B12",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "Which is equal to 28400 kHz?",
    "answers": [
      "28.400 kHz",
      "2.800 MHz",
      "284.00 MHz",
      "28.400 MHz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5B13",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which is equal to 2425 MHz?",
    "answers": [
      "0.002425 GHz",
      "24.25 GHz",
      "2.425 GHz",
      "2425 GHz"
    ]
  }
]